Guide to the Dr. Bill Wilson Collection, 1979-2008 UA 449
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Dr. Bill Wilson Collection
1979-2008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Wilson, Bill
UA 449
4 Linear Feet 4 boxes
This collection consists of four boxes containing books, media, and photographs documenting college history, student productions, and event from 1979 to 2008.
Biographical / Historical
William L. Wilson, known to generations of Rice University students as Dr. Bill, was professor of electrical engineering at Rice University from 1972 and Resident Associate of Wiess College from 1978 until his retirement from Rice in 2006. He also served as interim Master of Wiess in 1983 and in a myriad of formal and informal roles on the Rice campus throughout his teaching career. The keeper of many Wiess traditions, he was arguably the most influential person in the college's history.
A native of Long Island, William L. Wilson Jr. grew up in Princeton, New Jersey, and came to Rice in 1972 after earning his bachelor's, master's, and doctoral degrees in electrical engineering at Cornell University. In 1978 he became a Resident Associate at Wiess College, one of the university's residential colleges. Wiess remained his home until 2006, when Dr. Bill retired to his long-time summer home in Vermont.
Source: https://en-academic.com/dic.nsf/enwiki/3795806
Content Description
This collection consists of four boxes containing documents, books, media, and photographs documenting college history, student productions, and events that include: CDs, DVDs, VHS tapes, audio cassettes,magazines, directories, Wiess RA correspondence, WTT records A/V specs Wiess table top lightboard, Weiss history, map, as well as materials documenting events at Hanszen, Sid Rich, Jones, and Lovett colleges from 1979 to 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Doward Hudlow, December 2021
Arrangement
The materials in this collection have been arranged in two series as follows:
Series I: Media Series II: Documents
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
compact discs; digital moving image formats; books; photographs; audiotapes; directories
- Series I: Media
  - Subseries A: Baker College
    - Rice Symphonic Band, 1998-12-03 (Box 1)
    - King Lear Acts I and 2, 2003-03-29 (Box 1)
    - Baker Shakespeare "Othello"- Acts I, 2 and 3, 2004-03-19 (Box 1)
    - "Hello Again", n.d. (Box 1)
    - "We are That" Jazz Night, 1994-02-12 (Box 1)
  - Subseries B: Hanszen College
    - Hanszen RVG Concert, 1996-04-18 (Box 1)
    - Hanszen Talent Show, 1997-04-17 (Box 1)
    - "Guys and Dolls", 1999-11-17 (Box 1)
    - Kiss Me Kate- Act I, 2003-10-31 (Box 1)
    - Kiss Me Kate- Act II PG, 2003-10-31 (Box 1)
    - Kiss Me Kate- Act II R, 2003-10-31 (Box 1)
    - La Cage aux Folles, 2005-11-11 (Box 1)
    - Fantastics Mix, 1982-09-12 (Box 1)
  - Subseries C: Jones College
    - "Apple Tree", 2003-03-01 (Box 1)
    - "Assassins", 2004-03-27 (Box 1)
    - Night of Scenes, 2004-11-19 (Box 1)
  - Subseries D: Lovett College
    - Godspell, 1998-05-07 (Box 1)
    - Best Little Whorehouse in Texas- Act 1 and 2, 1998-11-21 (Box 1)
    - Pre-Med, the Musical, 2000-03-21 (Box 1)
    - "Little Shop of Horrors", 2002-11-08 (Box 1)
    - You're a Good Man Charlie Brown!, 2003-10-24 (Box 1)
    - The Vagina Monologues, 2004-02-13 (Box 1)
    - Picasso at the Lapin Agile, 2004-04-02 (Box 1)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 2004-10-28 (Box 1)
    - Inherit the Wind, 2005-11-18 (Box 1)
  - Subseries E: Sid Richardson College
    - Go Daddy-O Week Swing into Sid Richardson College, 1999 (Box 1)
    - A New Brain Sid Rich Spring, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Sid Music Nite, 2002-04-30 (Box 1)
    - City of Angels- Acts 1 and 2, 2003-02-28 (Box 1)
    - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas- Acts 1 and 2, 2004-02-21 (Box 1)
    - Powder Puff Final Sid, 2004-12-05 (Box 1)
    - A New Brain, 2005-02-25 (Box 1)
    - Brewster McCloud, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Subseries F: Wiess College
    - Hello Hamlet, Cassette, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet, CD, DVD, VHS, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet, CD, DVD, VHS, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Wiess CD 1 and 2, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Wiess XFer, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet, CD, DVD, VHS, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Rice Concert Jazz Band, 1990-11-04 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet, CD, DVD, VHS, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Jazz Nite 1 and 2, 1993-09-24 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Jazz Nite CD, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Burnt Toast- Skank and Splank, 1995-03-25 (Box 1)
    - Latin Jazz 1, 1995-04-08 (Box 1)
    - Jazz Nite, 1995-04-22 (Box 1)
    - Wiess College Nite, 1995-04 (Box 1)
    - Lara Bruckmann, 1995-05-07 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Jazz Nite 1 and 2, 1996-04-19 (Box 1)
    - College Nite Spring, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet CD, DVD, VHS, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet, CD, DVD, VHS (Mix), 1996 (Box 1)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, 1997-04-04 (Box 1)
    - Jazz Nite 1 and 2, 1997-04-19 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Nite at Coffee House, 1997-10 (Box 1)
    - "A Chorus Line", 1998-03-28 (Box 1)
    - Latin Jazz 2, 1995-04-08 (Box 1)
    - Jazz Nite 1 and 2, 1998-04-18 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Musical Taste of Talent, 1998-10-27 (Box 1)
    - Larry Sleazak Quintet Live at Wiess College JazzNite, 1999-04-24 (Box 1)
    - Smoking Guns at Wiess JazzNite, CD, Cassette, 1999-04-24 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Musical, Cassette, 1999-10-12 (Box 1)
    - A Taste of Talent Wiess Musical Performances, CD, 1999-10-12 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Nite at Coffee House, 1999-11-09 (Box 1)
    - Wake Up Seniors!, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Musicale, 2000-03-13 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet, CD, Cassette, VHS, 2000-03-24 (Box 1)
    - The David Herman Quintet, 2000-04-15 (Box 1)
    - The David Dash Quartet, 2000-04-15 (Box 1)
    - Jose Miguel and Friends, 2000-04-15 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Recital, 2000-10-02 (Box 1)
    - Wake Up Seniors!, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Wiess House Files, 2001-08 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Musicale, 2001-11-15 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Photos, 2002-01 (Box 1)
    - She Loves Me, 2002-04-12 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Soiree, 2002-09-28 (Box 1)
    - Company, 2003-04-04 (Box 1)
    - Freshman One-Acts, 2003-10-03 (Box 1)
    - Wiess College Music Soiree, 2003-10-04 (Box 1)
    - Art- Original, 2003-11-21 (Box 1)
    - Art- Post Version, 2003-11-21 (Box 1)
    - Art Photos, 2003-11 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Jazz Nite, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet Background, CD. VHS, 2003-2004 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Jazz Nite, CD, 2004-04-17 (Box 1)
    - Freshman One Acts, 2004-10-15 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Musicale, 2004-10-16 (Box 1)
    - Beyond Therapy Christopher Durang, 2004-11-18 (Box 1)
    - Wiess O-Week, 2004 (Box 1)
    - Wiess Pics, 2004 (Box 1)
    - Caberet, 2005-03-26 (Box 1)
    - Freshman 1- Acts, 2005-10 (Box 1)
    - The Foreigner, 2005-11-17 (Box 1)
    - Beer Bike, 2005 (Box 1)
    - Chris Williams In Memorium, 2006-09-07 (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet, DVD, 2008 (Box 1)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, n.d. (Box 1)
    - A Little Night Music, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Burnt Toast- Mix, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Chicago- Master Mix, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Definitive Wiess Cabaret, CD, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Hello Hamlet Act 2, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Latin Jazz Mix, n.d. (Box 1)
    - The Team Awesome Band (Box 1)
    - TFW Warm-Ups, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Wiess 244, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Wiess Tabletop "Cabaret" Compilation, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Wiess Tabletop Theatre Presents Pippin, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Pippin Act 1, n.d. (Box 1)
    - Pippin- Mix 1, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Subseries G: Other Rice Events
    - 1 Acts, n.d. (Box 2)
    - 10 Cent Whore, n.d. (Box 2)
    - A Capella, 2002-03-20 (Box 2)
    - A Capella Festival, 2000-04-09 (Box 2)
    - "A Cappella 2000" Rice University Philharmonics, 2002-03-20 (Box 2)
    - "A Capella 2000" University of A&M Apotheosis, 2002-03-20 (Box 2)
    - "A Capella 2000" University of Georgia Accidentals, 2002-03-20 (Box 2)
    - A Fine Mess Conflicting Reports, n.d. (Box 2)
    - A Fine Mess Now What? The Final Mess, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Africa Closer Possession, 2001-12 (Box 2)
    - Andy, 2005-04-21 (Box 2)
    - Angels and Company Fleck (Box 2)
    - Annie Lin- Studio, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Annie Lin at Underground (Box 2)
    - Annie/ Bard, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Annoying Miss, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Ari's Sound Track (Box 2)
    - As the Wrench Turns, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Assassins 1, 2, 3, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Attention Deficit Jamfest, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Battle of the Bands, 2005-11-18 (Box 2)
    - Battle Sows Video Highlights, 2001-2002 (Box 2)
    - Bee Stung Lips, 1994-02 (Box 2)
    - Bee Stung Lips Recording Master, 1994-01-29 (Box 2)
    - Ben Horne and Jeff Giesenger Live at Underground (Box 2)
    - Ben Yuhas Dec Project, 2002-05 (Box 2)
    - Ben Yuhas December Stilness, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Best Little Whorehouse, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Bill Martin's Radio Performance Archives, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Black History, 2005-02 (Box 2)
    - Blazing Sackbuts, 2000-12-12 (Box 2)
    - Bourland CD (Box 2)
    - The Box; or the Denumerably Infinite Chorus of Professional Bridesmaids, 2003-04-20 (Box 2)
    - BSL Mix/ Deb Lutes Piano, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Burnt Toast, 1995-03-26 (Box 2)
    - Burnt Toast, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Butt Spelling Mix, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Butter Battles, 2001-03-17 (Box 2)
    - C and W Music- David Haves (Box 2)
    - Cabaret, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Cabaret Photos, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Campanile Moon/ Rough, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Cast Iron Filter, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Change the World DVD, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Charlie Brown, n.d. (Box 2)
    - City of Angels CD, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Clif Confident, 2001-04-23 (Box 2)
    - Clif Confident at Ovations, 2002-05-09 (Box 2)
    - Clifton Confident's ":"Last Sha-Bang!" (Concert Special), 2002 (Box 2)
    - CNX Tape, n.d. (Box 2)
    - COL's SNR Video, n.d. (Box 2)
    - College Meeting, 1998-09-14 (Box 2)
    - Conry Audio, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Cousin Mary, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
    - Dancin Boyz, 2005 (Box 2)
    - Daniel Kendis Audio Files Stella Demo (Box 2)
    - Daniel Kendis Files Demo (Box 2)
    - Daniel Kendis Project (Box 2)
    - The Dao + 1, 2003-12-06 (Box 2)
    - Dave Herman, 2002-04-20 (Box 2)
    - The Dave Herman Quintet, 2000-04-15 (Box 2)
    - Deb and David Lutes/ Rough Mix (Box 3)
    - Deb Lutes Piano, 1994-05-03 (Box 2)
    - Deb Lutes "The Tape", 1994-05-03 (Box 2)
    - Deborah and David Lutes Live Recording at Wilsound Studios, 1994-06-11 (Box 2)
    - Deborah Lutes, 1994-02-20 (Box 2)
    - Diversity Jazz Band (Box 2)
    - Duel, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Earnest- 3, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Edloe St., 2000-11-10 (Box 2)
    - Edloe Street Live at Undergrounds, 1999-02-05 (Box 2)
    - EE History, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Election Speeches, 2003-02-10 (Box 2)
    - Ellipsis, 2002-04-20 (Box 2)
    - Ellipsis, 2004-08 (Box 2)
    - Ellipsis #1, #2, #3, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Ellipsis CD J-Card Design, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Ellipsis "From the Inside Out", 2003-10-12-2003-10-13 (Box 2)
    - Ellipsis Scatch CD, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Eric, Jorge, Kevin Trio, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Ezra Charles Design for Living, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Faith/ FaFa SPRCAO, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Fellows 2, Spring, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Final Mix AIFF Files, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Final Mix L/R Files, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Food Service MTG, 1998-09 (Box 2)
    - The Freshmakers, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Freshman Songs, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Frosh Acts, 2004 (Box 2)
    - Frosh Pics, n.d. (Box 2)
    - G and S "Patience" (Box 2)
    - Grad CD, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Graduation Tape, n.d. (Box 2)
    - General Noise Jamfest, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Godspell, 1998-05-07 (Box 2)
    - Godspell Mix, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Gospelfest, 2003-02-01 (Box 2)
    - The Grapes of Wrath, 2005 (Box 2)
    - Guys and Dolls- WTT, 1985-03 (Box 2)
    - Hamlet 4, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Happy Birthday Emma, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Haze and John Henry Files (Box 2)
    - Hazel's Special CD, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Hello Hamlet, 2004 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band, 2000-04-09 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Concert, 2000-06-18 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Concert, 2000-10-22 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Concert, 2001-02-18 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Concert, 2002-06-16 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Fall Concert, 2003-10-05 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Flag Day, 1999-06-08 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Flag Day-Father's Day Concert, 2002-06-16 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band Rice Wind Ensemble, 1998-12-12 (Box 2)
    - Houston Concert Band XMas Concert, 2001-12-02 (Box 2)
    - Hudlow Slideshow, 2008-04-25 (Box 2)
    - Importance of Being Earnest, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Irie Time CD-5, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Irie Time- 'It's About Time", n.d. (Box 2)
    - Jamfest, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Jamfest, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Jamfest, 1995-04-21 (Box 2)
    - Jamfest, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Jamfest, 1998 (Box 2)
    - JamFest, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Jamfest Audio Master, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Jamfest Jams Vol. 1, 2, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Jamfest Movie, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Jazz Band, 2000-11-30 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Band Track 3= Jake A Train (Box 2)
    - Jazz Ensemble 6th Annual Latin Jazz Concert, 1999-04-21 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Ensemble 7th Annual Latin Jazz Concert, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Jazz Ensemble CoffeeHouse, 2000-03-01 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Ensemble Fall Concert, 2003-11-25 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Ensemble "Live at the Coffee House", 1998-11-04 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Ensemble "Live at the Coffee House", 2000-11-20 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Ensemble Spring Concert, 1999-03-04 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab, 2002-02-27 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab, 2002-04-11 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab Files, 2002-02-02 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab Band, 2000-04-20 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab Band, 2001-12-05 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab Band Coffee House, 2000-03-22 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab Band Concert, 2002-02-27 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab Band Concert, 2003-02-21 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Lab Band Spring, 2002-04-18 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite, 2003-04-12 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite Ellipsis, 2003-04-12 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite Ensemble, 2002-11-20 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite Sleazak, 2003-04-12 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite Larry Slezak, 2002-04-20 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite CD #1,2, 2005 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite Mix, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nite Sleazak Quintet, 1999-04-24 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Nites, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Jazz Quartet, n.d. (Box 2)
    - JLB, 2001-12-05 (Box 2)
    - JMYE Magnolia, 2004-12-09 (Box 2)
    - John Chao Master, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Jonathan Bourland (Box 2)
    - Jory, 2004-02-21 (Box 2)
    - Jory/ Laura, 2004-02-21 (Box 2)
    - Jose Miguel and Friends Files (Box 2)
    - Jose Miguel Jazz Nite Files, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Jose-Miguel Yamal Sextet Live at the Magnolia Room, 2004-12-09 (Box 2)
    - Joseph- Mix, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor (Box 2)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dream Coat Master Tape (Box 2)
    - L. John Doerr, 2000-03-31 (Box 2)
    - Lab Band, 2000-04-20 (Box 2)
    - L'arnest, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Lager Rythms, 1995-06-10 (Box 2)
    - Larry Ovations, 2004-10-22 (Box 2)
    - Larry Slezak Hammond Organ Band, 2004-10-22 (Box 2)
    - The Larry Slezak Hammond Organ Band at Ovations, 2004-11-26 (Box 2)
    - Larry Slezak Quartet, 2002-04-20 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz, 2000-04-07 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz, 2002-04-12 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz, 2001-03-23 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz Concert, 1997-04-11 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz Concert, 1998-04-18 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz Concert, 1999-04-21 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz Concert, 2001-03-23 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz Concert, 2002-04-12 (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz Master, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Latin Jazz Mix, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Laura, 2005-02-05 (Box 2)
    - Layabouts, 1997-04-30 (Box 2)
    - Leadership Road Trip Sound Track, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Los Soneros, 1994-03-17 (Box 2)
    - Lost (Now Found) Molly WAV's (Box 2)
    - Lunar New Year Year of the Monkey, 2004 (Box 2)
    - Mark Hirsch Demoted, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Mark Hirsch Electric, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Mark Hirsch Master, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Mark Hirsch Mix #1, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Marlo's DVD, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Meghan McGee, 2000-12-01 (Box 2)
    - Melodious Voices CD Image, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Melodious Voice of Praise, 1997-04-24 (Box 2)
    - Melodious Voices of Praise Good Friday Celebration, 2003-04-18 (Box 2)
    - Melodious Voices of Praise Songs of Thanksgiving, 2003-11-22 (Box 2)
    - Melodious Voices of Praise Spring Concert, 1999-04-24 (Box 2)
    - Mic Test Tape, n.d. (Box 2)
    - MOB Audio, 2001-01 (Box 2)
    - MOB- CD Master, 2001-03 (Box 2)
    - Moving On, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Music from Golden Gate, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Musicale, 2001-11-15 (Box 2)
    - National Public Radio "Morning Edition", 2002-01-30 (Box 3)
    - New Brain, 2000-02-28 (Box 3)
    - New Brain, 2005-02-25 (Box 3)
    - Nicholas Walker and Friends (Box 3)
    - Nick Anaya, 2002-04-20 (Box 3)
    - Original Foreigner, 1987-03 (Box 3)
    - Othello, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Ovations, 2004-10-22 (Box 3)
    - O-Week, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Partial Duo Backup, 2001-05 (Box 3)
    - Patience, 2006-01-15 (Box 3)
    - Peter Hundfeldt CD (Box 3)
    - Peter Huckfeldt Quartet, 2002-04-20 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics, 1998-01-25 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics 1, 2, 2000-04-16 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics A Capella, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics "A Scorching Day of Abstention", 2002 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics "All That Chaz", 2003 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics and the Ransom Notes A Capella Festival, 2000-04-09 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics "Bridges and Breakdowns" (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics CD Files, 2002-04 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Fund Raising Concert, 2001-02-04 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics ICCA Audition CD, 2004 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics ICCA, Durham, NC, 2004-01-31 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics ISAC Demo Disc 1st Mix, 2002-10-21 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Master, 1997-05-04 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics- Mix, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics "No Timidity", 2000 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Rice Chapel with Lager Rythms, 2003-11-07 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Songs, 2001-12 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics/ Spontaneous Combustion, 2002-11-22 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Spontaneous Combustion Joint Show, 2003-12-12 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Spring Audio, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics "The CD", 2001 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Test CD, 2000-11-28 (Box 3)
    - Philharmonics Undergrounds w/ Phils (Box 3)
    - Phils, 2001-02-04 (Box 3)
    - Phils, 2001-04-22 (Box 3)
    - Phils, 2004-12-05 (Box 3)
    - Phils, 2005-03-03 (Box 3)
    - Phils, 2005-05-01 (Box 3)
    - Phils, 2005-09-30 (Box 3)
    - Phils, 2002-02-10 (Box 3)
    - Phils Actually No Timidity, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Phils Chain/ My Lovin/ Possession/ Waterfalls (Box 3)
    - Phils Ellipsis #1, 2004-10-15 (Box 3)
    - Phils/ Fizz, 2001-03-13 (Box 3)
    - Phils Out, 2005-10 (Box 3)
    - Phils Power of Two/ Blackbird, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Phils Project, 2002-10-20 (Box 3)
    - Phils Request Concert, 2005-03-03 (Box 3)
    - Phils Spontaneous Cover, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Phils Study Break, 2005-03-01 (Box 3)
    - Phils Study Break Concert, 2004-12-05 (Box 3)
    - Phils Tracks, 2001-12-02 (Box 3)
    - Phils at Underground, 2004-10-15 (Box 3)
    - Phliogistan, 2001-03-01 (Box 3)
    - Phlogistan Uindicated, 2000-10-27 (Box 3)
    - Photos from Bronze, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Picasso 2, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Picasso at Lapin Sound Cues (Box 3)
    - Pirates #1-2, 5-6, n.d. (Box 3)
    - "Pre Med" CD, 2000-03-21-2000-03-22 (Box 3)
    - Prometheus at Sammy's, 1997-05-05 (Box 3)
    - Prometheus String Quartet, n.d. (Box 3)
    - PV/ CD, 2002-04-17 (Box 3)
    - RCB/ HCB, 2001-02-18 (Box 3)
    - RCB/ HCB, 2002-10-20 (Box 3)
    - RCB/ HCB Xmas Concert, 1999-12-05 (Box 3)
    - Red Jaundice, 1993-05-02 (Box 3)
    - Rice Concert Band, 2000-02-29 (Box 3)
    - Rice Concert Band Concert, 2000-10-22 (Box 3)
    - Rice Images, 2005 (Box 3)
    - Rice Jazz Ensemble, 1991-12-04 (Box 3)
    - Rice Jazz Ensemble, 1996-11-06 (Box 3)
    - Rice Jazz Ensemble, 1996-12-04 (Box 3)
    - Rice Jazz Ensemble, 1998-11-04 (Box 3)
    - Rice Jazz Ensemble, 1999-03-04 (Box 3)
    - Rice Light Opera Society Presents "Pirates of the Penzance", 2004-03-25 (Box 3)
    - Rice Symphonic Band, 2000-10-22 (Box 3)
    - Rice Symphonic Band February Concert the "Glorisa", 2000-02-29 (Box 3)
    - Rice Symphonic Band Lord O' Rings, 1999-02-21 (Box 3)
    - Rice Symphonic Band Spring Concert, 2000-04-09 (Box 3)
    - Rice Symphonic Band Symphony No. 1, Johan de Meij "The Lord of the Rings", 1999-02-21 (Box 3)
    - Richard Vella, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Riot Nerd at Undergrounds, 1999-04-09 (Box 3)
    - Rock Vote/ Choir/ Coffee, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Ronnie Segal Chicago Shots, n.d. (Box 3)
    - RSB/ HCB, 2001-10-21 (Box 3)
    - The Richard Vella Experience, n.d. (Box 3)
    - San Jacinto Music Colloquium, 2000-03-22 (Box 3)
    - Senior Slide Show, 2003 (Box 3)
    - Seniors Wake Up, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Seth and Ray Boy Band (Box 3)
    - Shrew, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Silicon Run 1, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Slezack/ Ovations, 2004-11-26 (Box 3)
    - Slezak/ Yamal Quartet at Ovations, 2004-06-04 (Box 3)
    - Smoking Guns Jamfest, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Smoking Guns Rough Mix, n.d. (Box 3)
    - SNR Slideshow, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Soiree, 2003-10-04 (Box 3)
    - Songs Commencement, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Sonny Rollins, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Soul Night DVD, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Spinal Tap, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Spont, 2005-03-03 (Box 3)
    - Spontaneous, 2004-12 (Box 3)
    - Spont. Comb., n.d. (Box 3)
    - Sprwal, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
    - Stab, 1994-01-22 (Box 3)
    - Stealth Shoot to Kill, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Stacy Kent "Boy Next Door", n.d. (Box 3)
    - Sturgeon Curse, n.d. (Box 3)
    - SwixMix, 2002-04-17 (Box 3)
    - Taylor Johnson's Fall Pics, 2005 (Box 3)
    - Ten Hands the Big One is Coming and Extras (Box 3)
    - Test Tone Tape, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Tomorrow's Pact Files, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Ultramagg, 1996-02-1997-06 (Box 3)
    - Undergrounds, 2000-09-28 (Box 3)
    - Undergrounds LIVE!, 1997-04-11 (Box 3)
    - Univ. w/ Credits, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Universal Joint deepenin', 1996 (Box 3)
    - Universified Act 1, n.d. (Box 3)
    - UTXporter, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Virtus Walk-Thru, n.d. (Box 3)
    - "Wake Up Seniors", 1998-05 (Box 3)
    - Wake Up Seniors, 1999-05 (Box 3)
    - Wake Up Seniors, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Wake Up Seniors!, 2004 (Box 3)
    - We are That, 1994-02-13 (Box 3)
    - Wet Paint, 1993-08-29 (Box 3)
    - Whorehouse 1, 2, 3, 4, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Wiess Boyz, n.d. (Box 3)
    - "Wit"- WTT, 2002-11-21 (Box 3)
    - Wonderful Preacher Man (Box 3)
    - WTT Freshman One Acts, 2002-09-28 (Box 3)
    - Yamal at Caezans, 2004-02-27 (Box 3)
- Series II: Documents
  - Composition Book, 1995-1997 (Box 4)
  - The Inauguration of George Rupp, 1985-10-25 (Box 4)
  - WTT Records, 1990-2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Play "The Author", n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Magazines, 1988-1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Directories, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Pippin Pics, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Wilsound Studios, 1990-2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Wilsound 2, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Headshots, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - P. Jones Map, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Rice Ally, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Wiess, 1992-2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Wiess RA Com, 1988-2006 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Wiess A/V Specs, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Wiess Tabletop Lightboard Instruction Manual, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Wiess Light BD #1, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Wiess History, 1976-2006 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Wiess Photos, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)